Ms. Choi
was the only adult
that was ever kind to me.
Everyone else had already given up on me,
but Ms. Choi was the only person
who believed I could be something more.
I realize now
the truth is that, all this time,
I was in love with Ms. Choi.
-You made it.
-Hm.
Why is it so dark in here?
Take this.
Thank you.
People who live alone
shouldn't live in the dark.
I just cooked up some fresh kimchi.
I ended up making too much,
and I know you love it.
Were you planning on feeding an army?
Jeez, I can't open it.
What?
-The knot's too tight.
-I didn't want it to leak.
Mission accomplished.
Would you like a drink?
Mr. Choi.
Once we become motivated by revenge…
it'll mean we've gone too far.
Hm.
Hwa-jin, I don't want to be forced
to tell you to forget about my daughter.
Yes, sir.
Come and sit down with me.
Let's have some of that kimchi I brought.
Is instant rice okay with you?
Are you really about to feed
your father-in-law some pre-cooked junk?
Well, you were the one
who made some last time I was over.
Don't talk back,
and make some crispy rice.
-Insolence.
-I'll buy some rice and come right back.
You don't have rice?
If you want crispy rice,
I can make it from the instant rice.
No, I don't want… I just want some…
Instant packs are just as good.
-I want freshly-cooked rice.
-Sure.
I eat instant every day.
Approval ratings
for the ERPB have surpassed 50%
for the first time.
In a survey
on potential presidential candidates,
Minister Choi Gang-seok's approval rating
has risen sharply
compared with his results
in the previous poll.
Some say that his views on educational
reform are just what the country needs.
That's right.
Although some still argue
that the ERPB has yet to prove
that they are not motivated by personal
vendettas, given that the core members
are both related to the teacher
who was murdered two years ago--
This looks so good. Ooh!
Don't you have hot water at your place?
No, this is just easier.
By the time I get home, it'll be perfect.
That's why I said I'd buy you dinner.
Well, sharing dinner with my boss
feels like work.
Hm.
Did I say that out loud?
Thank you for the kind comments.
I'll be sure to keep them in mind.
Sorry, sir, but is it okay
if I just… call it for tonight?
Why? I can drop you off.
Are you in a hurry?
It's just, every time we stay together,
there's always something that happens
which extends our work hours
on, and on, and on--
Just a minute.
What are they doing?
Looks like they're breaking into a car.
-Let's just contact the police.
-No, they're still in school uniforms.
Get a move on.
Deputy Bong, protect this with your life.
Uh, sir, what do you want me to do?
Stay there.
I was actually planning on going home
to clean my graphics card.
So, could I maybe--
Oh. You shouldn't have taken so much.
God, would you just stand up?
Yes! It's fucking open!
-Come on, please work.
-Let's go!
Yes! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Holy shit, we're-- Oh, shit!
-Stop.
-What the fuck?
-Guys, get out.
-Just move! Out of the way!
Get out of the way! Just--
What are you doing?
What is this, a water fight? Water guns?
-That's enough. Now get out.
-Stop that.
-Oh shit! Dude, it's just going.
-Stop the car.
Hey, watch out!
I'm just going forward. Look out!
-He's blocking my view now.
-Hey!
-Move out of the way!
-Stop the car now!
Look at this guy.
How is he holding on like that?
Would you just walk straight already?
Hey.
-Yeah?
-I work for the ERPB.
Tell me what you're doing with that girl.
You're with the ERPB?
Get out of the way! Get off!
Inspector, are you okay?
Those damn brats need to learn.
-Hey, get out of the way!
-Oh!
Dude, that was insane!
Woo-hoo!
Let's go! Whoo!
These fucking kids.
Catch up by foot!
What the hell?
Whoa, this is so messed up!
-Hold on back there!
-Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
You see how good I am? I should be
a professional race car driver!
-Hold tight! I'm gonna swerve this bitch!
-Oh fuck!
Whoo!
Please go slower, Inspector!
Holy shit. This guy isn't dead?
-No way.
-How?
Fucking light 'em up!
Hey! You kids stop the car!
Let's go! Shoot these fuckers!
Show 'em what we're working with.
-Fuck, it's burning my fingers!
-This is wild.
Oh! Oh!
Boom!
Whoa! Whoa!
I can't believe this.
Oh! Oh!
-Whoa.
-I got a gift for you! And all of you!
-Whoo! Fireball!
-Those kids, they just don't get it.
Fireball!
Whoo!
-Ha! Whoa!
-Ah! Ah. Oh!
Fireball!
Woo-hoo! Whoa!
Bang, bang!
Holy shit! That's, like,
the craziest thing we've done!
What the fuck?
Is the guy still behind us? Fuck!
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey ! Hey, whoa!
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on, don't stop!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh, whoa! Whoa!
Min-su, that was crazy.
How do you drive so good?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa, whoa!
Why are you still holding that?
Because if I don't, she'll kill me.
-Whoa!
-Watch out! You're spilling that.
-Hey!
-Whoa!
-Careful!
Pull over, now!
-You fuckers.
-Just get lost, fucking weirdo!
-You're never gonna stop us, you dumbass.
-Kids are flipping me off.
-Whoa, please slow down!
-Come on.
You ain't gonna do nothing.
-Oh!
-Move out of the way!
I'm gonna hit them!
Goddamn it!
Oh shit.
What are you doing?
I think I broke my leg.
Whoa!
Turn the car off now!
Who are you?
Juvenile offenders.
-What?
-We're 14, actually.
Huh.
Everybody step back.
Give the police some space.
INCHEON GANGHWA POLICE STATION
We were simply
stopping for some food, and by chance…
Careful, miss.
Please stay awake. Are you all right?
One thing led to another, and my colleague
managed to throw a bike,
and it got stuck under their car.
Are you all right?
We need you to stay awake.
Leave her. Yun-jin's just drunk.
She drank three bottles or something.
-No, she drank way more.
-Yeah, she drank a lot.
Seriously, though, you guys
are acting like we wanted to hurt her,
but we didn't do anything like that.
We're all friends.
-Exactly.
-Right.
Are they really your friends?
Yes, they're my friends.
So just leave us alone, okay?
See, I wasn't lying. She just told
you we're friends. We're like besties.
-Yeah.
-Enough!
You guys are guilty of car theft,
driving without a license,
and violating traffic laws.
-We're very sorry, sir!
-So sorry, sir.
But we only drove it out of curiosity
since it was already running.
That's right.
So it's really not our fault.
We just did it
because of our raging hormones.
-Because of puberty.
-It was out of our control.
Seriously, we are deeply remorseful
for what we did.
Please forgive us.
Please forgive us. Please forgive us.
-Do you think we're gonna fall for this?
-Im Han-rim. That's enough.
They know that they won't be punished
for saying this.
He's right. These kids
have been here many times already.
And since they're juvenile offenders,
they know we can't press charges.
They always claim they didn't know what
they were doing, so we can't charge them.
Isn't that right?
-You spoke to the parents?
-Yes.
Gonna be a while before they're here.
Well, actually our homeroom teacher
will be here soon.
-Hand them over once he's here.
-Yes, sir.
-Chief?
-Yeah?
So, what are you gonna do about them?
We've already tried to send
some of their cases to juvenile court,
but for now all we can do is wait
and let them off with a warning.
I heard the school was having
the same problem with them.
Speak of the devil.
-You can ask him yourself.
-Good Evening, Mr. Lee.
CUSTODY HANDOVER CONFIRMATION FORM
He's full of shit.
We'll be on our way now.
I want all of you in my office tomorrow
so we can talk about what happened.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for taking care of us.
-Thank you very much!
-Thank you.
-We'll take our leave now.
-Get her home safely.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's an uncomfortable sight, huh?
It happens so much.
It's hard to get used to.
I hear you're from the ERPB?
Yes, we are. I'm Inspector Na Hwa-jin.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but it appears that you two
will need to write
an additional statement.
Those kids reported you.
-What for?
-For child abuse.
These days, kids can report you
through an app if they want.
You're kidding me?
I'm sorry about what happened.
I should have taught them better.
Don't worry. I'm sure you tried your best.
I'm embarrassed to admit this
as a teacher,
but the school has no idea
what to do with these kids.
They can get away with whatever they want.
They know that adults can't do anything.
Isn't there anything you can do
as their teacher?
They know, as minors,
they can't be liable for their crimes,
and schools can't change that.
And the fact that middle school
is mandatory, it'd be hard to expel them.
Sir!
-So you were outsmarted by some kids?
-Yes, sir.
I've heard about how much juvenile
offenders are allowed to get away with.
Maybe I put too much faith
in ex-Special Forces agents.
Whoa, my turn! My turn!
Who are those kids?
The ones we were talking about.
The same ones that bested us.
Try to catch us now!
Hello, guys.
Good luck with your car!
They seem fun.
-Their school was Hyeonjin Middle School?
-Yeah.
We start work there tomorrow.
Jung Seung-jin.
Yo, you don't wanna say hi to me?
Oh, uh, sorry.
You lookin' at me?
Did I hit you?
-No, no, you didn't.
-Of course I did, you stupid idiot.
Would you look at that?
Ah, good morning.
-Hello.
-Morning.
-And who's your new friend?
-I'm Jung Seung-jin.
Jung Seung-jin, off you go.
-Get to class.
-Okay.
Make sure to put my stuff on my desk.
Hey, you should try to skip school
once in a while.
You know, give the other students
an opportunity to breathe.
You guys actually came, then.
I'm surprised.
Well, given how kind you were yesterday,
we came here
to return the favor to you guys.
What's that?
Starting today, we will be
investigating this school. You guys ready?
-We can't right now.
-How come? Too busy?
Actually, we're free. Right, guys?
Okay. Come with me.
-"Come with me!"
-We get to skip class.
We're gonna be famous.
I'm gonna get so many followers.
I don't have
a signature yet for autographs.
I told you
we were investigating this school.
I got it. You're trying
to buy some time, aren't you?
-It's like in the movies.
-He lied about the investigation.
They're just keeping us away from everyone
while they get statements from students.
Look at you.
Aren't you a smart little guy?
Since you already know, why not confess?
Just do what you need to do, Inspector.
Say thank you, okay?
Anything you say
will be kept confidential.
Tell me about Min Ji-ung's gang.
Have you ever been attacked by these guys?
Or seen them attack other kids?
I've never seen anything.
I haven't, no.
We're not really friends,
so I can't help you.
-Please just leave me alone.
-I'm sorry, but I don't know.
No, never.
Han-rim,
I asked around about Yun-jin
like you asked me to.
And while she does seem
to hang out with Min Ji-ung, well,
they're not exactly friends.
-And if they're not friends--
-What are they, then?
Honestly, I didn't really
learn anything more.
Do you know where I can find her?
That's the thing. She should be here,
but she's not in class.
-Do you know where this is?
-Near the recycling bins.
I don't think she's there.
Look at the other cameras.
Usually these kinds of gangs
look for hideouts in places
that are isolated from everything else.
They hang out in places where the cleaners
and maintenance people work.
Easier to hide from the teachers there.
Well, if we take that
into consideration then,
here maybe?
What is this place?
It's a utilities building,
not far from the gym.
Oh!
I think this might be it.
Look over here.
Oh.
Here, it's this way. Oh.
Oh! There should be the key around here.
Are you in there?
Stand back.
What?
Han-rim! Oh. What are you…
What are you doing?
Here. I'll take that.
Can I ask what you were doing in there?
Was it Min Ji-ung who locked you in?
Why were you with them yesterday?
We were out drinking.
Then how come
I didn't smell any alcohol on you?
And if you hadn't been drinking
last night,
why were you stumbling around like that?
Can I see what's in your bag?
What? No.
Hey, take it easy.
Can you tell me what this is?
They're just vitamins.
Oh, that's good to know. Then I'm sure
you wouldn't mind if I took one.
I've been working late recently.
I wanna make sure I'm healthy.
No, don't take that!
If I shouldn't take it, then you
shouldn't be taking these vitamins either.
Were you on these pills yesterday?
That why you were stumbling?
Yun-jin, were you high on these drugs?
-Hey, Yun!
-Hey!
Ah!
Whoa, you look so pretty today.
-Did you change your eye shadow? Or blush?
-Blush. Doesn't it look good?
It looks so good.
You look like the popular girls.
You really do.
Just lose a bit of weight.
It's too late for me.
But if you lose a bit of weight,
you could be like a celebrity!
I don't know.
I think I'm having a growth spurt.
I've been so hungry lately.
Oh.
Yeah, we kind of see it
on the Shorts you post.
No, for real?
You could kinda see it a bit.
Then I guess this is day one of starting
my diet until I become a celebrity.
-You say that every time.
-This time, I'm serious.
CHEWY COOKIES
DUBAI CHOCOLATE
You're not eating today?
Oh, you're broke. Is that it?
No, I'm just trying to lose some weight.
You'd be a lot prettier if you did.
Do you really think so?
You shouldn't be starving yourself
to lose weight. I have a better way.
Here.
Just take some of these.
Someone I know lost 40 pounds with this.
I stole a few pills without them knowing.
All I know is
they lost 40 pounds like nothing.
And apparently,
all your favorite celebrities,
they're taking them too.
Just take one pill.
It'll change your whole life.
There's no way it could be bad for you.
It's a cute little heart.
Try it. Come on.
Put it in water.
You can pay me back if it works.
-If you don't want it, give it--
-Wait.
TYPICAL DANCE SKILLS
OF A MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL
Yun-jin.
I saw your Short, and you looked so good.
Did the pill work?
I think it worked.
Well, that's great to hear.
Do you want some more?
Do you have some?
Of course I do.
Heart for you.
Ji-ung, do you think
you could get me some of those pills?
Well, sure I can. But it'll cost ya.
These things aren't free.
I'll pay for it.
-How much are they?
-Thirty thousand.
That's 50 now.
What?
Hm.
Let's fucking go! Fuck yeah.
So, do you think
you could give me some pills?
I don't have the money now,
but I'll pay you back later.
It's not a fucking charity, bitch.
Sorry?
I was just kidding. It was a joke.
Did I scare you?
But you know, if you don't have any money,
how about you work for it?
Is your job too hard?
Is it empty up there?
Huh?
You just give them the drugs,
take the money, and then come back here.
Is that so fucking hard?
Oh my God, you guys
just wanna piss me off, don't you? Huh.
Yo, Yun-jin! I'm really hoping
that you won't disappoint me.
Show me the money.
Come on.
Huh. Not bad.
-I want you to raise the price by 20,000.
-Twenty thousand?
That's too much.
Are you a fucking dumbass by any chance?
You still bought it, didn't you?
Raise it. They'll still buy them.
Well, say something.
Could I
maybe stop doing this, please?
-Ah.
-I'm just so scared. Please, I don't--
Fuck. No!
Give me the drugs.
-What?
-The drugs, give them to me.
Since you wanna quit so bad, I guess
you won't be needing these anymore.
Ha!
Look at that.
That's 50,000 won.
So, Yun-jin,
should I give you another chance?
All right.
What a waste.
-What's this bullshit?
-It's so boring.
-Take it seriously.
-You're not trying.
Fucking apply yourself.
SCHOOL POLICE REPORTING BOX
-Yeah, take 'em!
-And never come back!
-My bad, my bad.
-Stop that. Stop that. The cops.
Is that really them?
They're driving off with them.
-Goodbye!
-I hope he gets expelled at least.
-That's the minimum.
-Or have him transfer schools.
-Any idea who reported them?
No idea,
but I'm grateful to whoever it was.
Heat transfers
from the object with a high temperature
to one with a lower temperature.
There are three ways that this happens.
First, let's look at conduction.
When we typically sit down to eat,
we grill some meat, right?
When the meat touches
the high-temperature grill,
the particles of the meat that are
making contact begin moving more rapidly,
and each particle is transferred in turn.
Good morning, sir.
Yeah, sit down.
All right, let's continue with the lesson.
Bitch!
Thought we wouldn't find out
you reported us to the cops?
Yeah, that's right.
They told us about the letter you sent.
Now we have problems because of you.
Lucky for me,
I'm a minor, so they let me go.
Did you think
we'd end up in jail or something?
Keep dreaming.
We're minors.
We're not c… c… c… criminals
in the eyes of the law.
No!
Get in there.
See you later.
Ji-ung! Ji-ung, please!
Please open the door. I'm sorry, Ji-ung!
Ji-ung?
I know I was wrong.
Please, just open the door.
Ji-ung.
If you know that you were wrong…
…accept your punishment.
You understand, don't you, Yun-jin?
Hey, how about a group photo
to remember this moment?
-Ah, I'm starving. Let's get some food.
-Yeah, same. I'm down for whatever.
-What you wanna eat?
-Tonkatsu?
Can you testify
to everything you just said?
-It's the only way to punish them.
-I've done that before. There's no point.
Our teacher, the school, even the police,
couldn't do anything to stop them.
Every time, it just got worse for me.
Every time, I thought,
"This is it. It'll finally be over."
But each time, he came back to school.
In the end, it's always me that suffers.
The only way I'll escape is if I die.
I promise you it'll be different.
Your well-being is the priority
for all of us here at the Bureau.
You need to believe in us.
I'll take care of you.
We're done, sir.
WRITTEN STATEMENT
GO FUCK YOURSELF
I see that you boys
took this very seriously.
Of course we did, sir.
It isn't just about the bullying
and the beatings.
They're selling drugs to the kids.
They get the other kids addicted
and then they make them sell pills.
That's how they're making their money.
You sell drugs, huh?
Yeah. And what if we do?
Is that a problem, sir?
Oh, it is.
I'm sorry. I… I didn't know.
But, you know, because we're still kids,
this is when we should mess up.
We're just some kids
figuring it out as we go.
It's hard to understand
the difference between
what's wrong or right, you know?
You should choose
your next words very carefully.
I'm running out of patience, kid.
Oh, is that so?
Unfortunately, I can't stop now
since I really need the money.
I'll just keep doing it
until I'm an adult, okay? Then I'll stop.
I promise you. Really.
All right, all right, relax.
Well, if it bothers you that much…
…lock me up.
Take me away and throw me in jail.
But you can't, can you?
You just have to let us go.
-That's right.
-You must be so mad.
Fucked up, isn't it?
And listen, and learn
And listen, and learn, repeat
Listen, and learn
And listen, and learn…
Get the fuck away from me!
Daddy, help!
Welcome!
-Hey, you did a great job today.
-You go in the back. Go sit over there.
-You think you can fuck with us?
-Better pray we don't catch you.
Listen, and learn
And listen, and learn
And listen, and learn, repeat…
-Thanks for joining us.
-Shit.
And listen, and learn, repeat
Listen…
You better keep running!
And listen, and learn…
Stay away!
Han-rim? What are you doing here?
It's been a while.
Don't come near me.
I'll fucking kill all of you.
Whoo!
Min Ji-ung, you're being charged with
the crimes of inciting school violence,
the sale of narcotics,
coercing students into distributing drugs,
and turning your school
into a living hell.
So, from this point on…
you are in for a real treat.
Dude, what the fuck? Where are we?
Where are we going?
How would I know?
I have no idea where we are.
Thank you for your hard work!
Come on, move it.
Hey, you better tell us
where the fuck we are.
START OVER WITH A DREAM
Welcome, everyone, to the only
juvenile detention center in Korea.
You serious? You brought us to jail?
You thought you'd be able to avoid this?
It's time for you
to learn an important lesson.
Hey, Inspector. Everything's set.
Okay. Let's go.
-Can he do this?
-Park the truck.
-Oh, nice to meet you.
-I… I'm not sure about this.
GIMCHEON JUVENILE PRISON
IS REQUESTED TO COOPERATE
I don't know.
Minister, do you think
the public will accept it?
I'll take responsibility.
I'm sure you know this
better than anyone, Minister.
The reason we protect minors.
If what you're planning on doing
ever got leaked to the public,
the reaction would be terrible.
This could lead
to abuse and gross negligence charges.
Is that a good enough reason
to do nothing?
One of us needs to be the adult.
We need to show these kids
that there are consequences.
I need your support on this.
Minister.
STUDENT RECORD
MIN JI-UNG
-Name?
-Yoon Min-su?
It's Min Ji-ung.
Hyundai Apartments in Samseong, Gangnam.
Place all accessories into the basket.
-Ji-ung] When do we leave?
-Feet onto the markers.
Pull down your underwear and squat down.
A little further back.
And now, put your underwear back on.
Take your belongings and move along. Next!
Like you heard, pull down your underwear.
More, more, more, more, more.
A little more.
Squat down
and lift your backside up a bit.
Remove your underwear.
Oh shit.
Ugh!
NAME: CHOI U-SEONG
HOPE-DRIVEN CORRECTION
THAT OPENS DOORS TO BRIGHTER FUTURES
Inmates, stand up straight!
Cool! Cool!
From this point forward,
you will be treated
with the same consideration
as the other prisoners here.
You shall receive the same
mandatory physical and academic education,
and you will be required
to perform volunteer work.
Do you understand that?
Any comments?
Those with comments
can keep quiet. Let's go.
-Follow me.
-Forward!
We got fresh meat!
-Hey, you motherfucker!
-Hey!
DAILY REFLECTION AS A WAY OF LIFE
There's no fucking way!
Holy shit!
Listen up. Inspector Im Han-rim
will now educate all of you
on your current shared living space.
You fuckers think
you can get away with this?
Once we're out of here, I'm reporting you
for everything you did. All of you.
So, ma'am, are you ready
to face the consequences?
-Would you shut your mouth?
-Well, I might if you let us go!
You only have one way of getting out.
I'll let you go if you defeat me.
-What?
-I guess I'll leave you guys alone.
-What? Wait.
-Come on.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Sir, wait up! Inspector, hold on!
I mean, I know that they're just kids,
but there's still four of them in there.
Aren't you worried?
I am worried. Hm. It could be dangerous
for the four boys.
Hm.
Just fucking do it, man.
-Ha!
-Whoa!
-Damn, bitch is fast!
-Ah, fuck!
Ha!
Agh, stop! Please, it hurts!
When an inmate uses violence
against an officer,
said officer can use violence
against the inmate.
In other words, legally speaking,
I can beat the shit out of all of you.
Ow, that stings!
Agh, stop!
Goddammit!
If you think it's unfair,
you can all attack me at once.
There's probably nothing I'd love more
than to beat up all of you, huh?
Uh…
-You'll wake up at 6:30.
-What?
Roll call will be conducted for
30 minutes. Breakfast will begin at 7 a.m.
For the following three hours, you will be
attending to your favorite tasks.
At 13:00 hours, you will exercise
and receive medical treatment,
and at 14:00 hours,
you'll partake in a few special classes.
After training, you will attend
information technology classes.
Yawning in class is prohibited.
No messing around with school supplies.
Your choice.
Inspector Im Han-rim!
Okay, Deputy Bong.
Inmates, assemble now!
That's not long enough. Again!
SSD. Ever heard of it?
It's what's known
as a memory storage device.
Inspector Im Han-rim!
No, I've got it here. It's the hard disk--
Outside, now!
Left, left, left.
You got ten seconds. And time!
Three, two, one, zero.
-Time's up!
-Wait, no!
-Looks to me like you didn't write it all.
-Inmates, assembly outside, now!
We just wanna study, okay?
I want all this cleaned up
by the end of the day.
Is this really the best you can do?
-How are we supposed to clear all this?
-Faster. Come on! Get this done properly.
What the hell are you doing?
Quit wasting your breath talking!
Ugh, this heat is killing me!
Seriously, we're gonna die out here.
I can't feel my hands.
-Come on. We don't have all day.
-Let's go. Move!
-Whoa!
-What the fuck you looking at?
-Look at the fucking ground.
-Those guys have red tags on their shirts.
What does a red tag mean?
It means these guys are killers.
It's unbelievable.
There's so many of them.
What the fuck are we doing here?
What? Are you complaining already?
Maybe tell them
that you're juvenile offenders.
Let's see if that works.
Everybody, listen up!
As of today, these juvenile offenders
will get their meals before everyone else.
Are you fucking joking?
-No, we don't have to.
-Go.
I said go.
All right, come on. Let these boys
come to the front of the line.
-Hurry up!
-Come on. You wanna eat? You bitches.
You stupid fuck.
You boys love sausages, don't you?
Make sure to enjoy them.
Young perps like you need to eat
lots a protein to grow. Isn't that right?
Have all the sausages you want.
You're special guests here.
-Fucks are taking everything!
-Looks like now we're all out.
Fuck!
I expect each and every one of you
to be kind.
These guys are juvenile offenders.
That means that these boys
can do whatever they want.
Now the rest of you will be served
rice, kimchi and salad, so eat up.
I said open your mouth!
-There you go.
-Eat!
-Dude, the fuck?
-This is bullshit.
-Fuck this shit!
-Hey!
Don't do that. You're nobody's slave.
Dude, I just wanna go home.
Fuck's sake.
You gotta clean this stuff.
The guys that work in the kitchen
told me that they're quite greasy
so we'd appreciate it if you could
wash these ones with a little extra care
as soon as you can.
Uh, you'll need to make sure
you clean the grains of rice,
'cause they get really sticky.
If you scrape them off like this,
it works pretty well.
I'll leave you to it.
How long are we gonna stay here?
Are you gonna keep crying,
you fucking shit?
Does my dad even know I'm here?
Why hasn't he come to get us?
-He'd already be here if he knew.
-It's illegal to keep him in the dark.
So putting minors like us
in jail is legal? Huh?
And this asshole
wants us to do the fucking dishes.
These guys are fucked
when my dad finds out!
That's the thing.
They don't know.
-So let's make sure they know.
-How do we do that?
There has to be some way.
They'll keep piling up
if you don't clean them.
-My eyes!
-Are you kidding me?
-Sorry about that.
-The fuck do you think you are?
I'm already pissed with this place,
and now you're getting on my nerves.
Listen. You guys
are way younger than me, all right?
You think I fucking care you're older?
Go on, do it yourself.
Do it! Go on! I scared him.
What, are you scared? You should be!
Hey, Ji-ung, relax!
Don't do it. Just let him go, Ji-ung.
Stop! Get out of there.
Fucker!
Hey, get off each other! Get off now!
What happened here?
Tell me what's going on.
I fell down, sir.
-You're saying Min Ji-ung did nothing?
-Correct, sir!
The inmate was just trying
to help me out of the water.
-What the hell--
-Thank you.
I won't ever forget this.
What is he…
Min Ji-ung.
About what happened earlier, are you sure
you didn't have anything to do with it?
You can mess with the others if you want,
but don't ever mess with that guy.
What if I do?
You'll be sure to regret it.
Kim Su-gyeom. Doesn't ring a bell?
He started out
as a victim of bullying himself.
Then, one day,
he decided that he had enough.
He killed every one of them.
Get the fuck outta here, loser!
What the fuck are you doing?
Get the fuck away from me!
He's gone crazy!
Go! Go! Go!
Move! Move!
Holy shit, I remember this story.
It was all over the news.
He's the bully killer! It's him!
As long as you had you nothing to do with
it, maybe you should stay out of his way.
Hey, watch it!
-Sir, nothing.
-Nothing here.
-Nothing here either!
A spoon has gone missing, so
we will be conducting a full body search
on each of you until we find it.
Got that?
A spoon can be modified
and used as a weapon.
We're doing this for your safety. Begin.
-It's that guy!
-Keep your hands on your head!
I saw him taking a spoon earlier
when we were cleaning.
I'm sure he has it on him.
Step aside.
Turn around. Hands on your head.
It's in his left pocket. The left one.
Toothpaste.
Hey, kid. Next time, you should think
before you speak. Am I clear?
Get back to the search. Back in line.
-Eyes to the front!
-Face forward. Hands on head.
-Don't make me repeat myself.
-Face to the wall.
-Don't mess with me.
-Hands on your head!
Nothing here.
Move! Get out of the way!
I'm already serving the maximum sentence,
so killing another person
won't change anything for me.
Get away from him!
Everyone inside!
You can't escape me, kid.
I'll make this your personal hell!
-I can play these games forever.
-Get him off now!
There's a lot of guys like me in here.
We're gonna have fun together.
I'll see you around!
MINISTRY OF EDUCATION
The enemy of human rights!
The Bureau must apologize.
Apologize! Apologize!
The enemy of human rights!
The Bureau must apologize! Apologize!
Hey, we want answers!
Don't run away from us! Minister!
Minister! Minister!
Hey, you can't leave like this!
You come back here, now!
-You can't run away!
-Hey! We're not leaving!
We'll stay here all day!
Minister! Minister. Hey, wait up.
Wait! You have to talk to us!
-We want answers!
-Answer our questions, Minister.
Minister, we want answers. Is it true
that you sent our children to a real jail?
That's correct.
How dare you
do something so cruel to my child?
Think of it as a field trip.
That's where they'll end up anyways.
Oh, come on! Are you hearing
what you're saying right now?
You think you can do this to our children
without asking for permission?
Would you have granted permission
if we had asked?
-What?
-At least you should've told us!
I can't believe your arrogance!
-This is bullshit.
-You've got some choice words for us.
Since you enjoy writing so much,
write about what your wonderful children
did to deserve being sent to jail.
-What did you say?
-I can't believe what I'm hearing.
What makes you think
you'll get away with this?
I will use whatever power I have
to have you removed from office,
so you can look forward to that!
You really think that
because you're a minister, it'll save you?
There's no need to threaten him.
We don't need to. We'll just inform
the press and Congress will do the rest!
You're absolutely right.
You scared now? Huh? Asshole!
We'll talk about that tomorrow
when you come visit the school.
School? Why the hell should we listen
to anything you have to say to us?
You'll go because it'll be
your last chance to see your children.
Then again, it's up to you.
-What did you say?
-The last chance to--
-What does he mean?
-Say that one more time!
Minister, you come back here right now!
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
Go inside.
-Mom!
-Dad! Oh my God!
-Dad!
-Oh, Ji-ung!
You do not answer any of the questions.
-My goodness! My sweetheart.
-Are you all right?
You don't look healthy.
You don't look like you've been eating.
No, it's okay.
I'm right here. Daddy's right here.
What did they do to your hair?
And your clothes? How dare they?
Minister, what's going on here?
Why are our children dressed like this?
I've heard what you did to them.
You took away their phones, and locked
them up, and made them wash dishes.
He doesn't even wash dishes at home!
You kept them in the same prison
as thieves and dangerous criminals!
How dare you do that to my son?
How could you send young 14-year-old boys
to a jail with criminals?
They're just children.
Juvenile offenders have rights!
All right.
Do you know what this is?
What the hell is that?
Tell your parents.
They're just diet pills.
The other kids wanted them.
They asked me to get them.
They threatened me.
It's not my fault!
Stop that!
Let go of my son!
What the hell is the matter with you?
Oh my God, sweetheart. Are you okay?
-Oh my God.
-I swallowed it. Shit!
What's going on?
Momma, I'm gonna die!
What's wrong? What happened?
Aren't they diet pills?
Scared of losing a little weight?
Sweetheart, what's going on?
-Mom, call an ambulance, quick!
-They're just vitamins. Don't worry.
You can relax.
What do you mean they were vitamins?
Fuck. Mom, I'm screwed. He set me up.
Seems like you know
you shouldn't be taking those pills.
I thought I was gonna die.
You have to help me.
They look identical
to the pills they were selling at school.
Phentermine, a drug
available by prescription only.
These are the drugs
they pushed on the other kids.
Mom. I… I really didn't know, Mom.
Honestly, I had no idea, Mom.
Mom!
My son said he didn't know!
They're children who made
a few mistakes, all right?
They're kids. They're young.
They don't know better.
They don't understand the consequences of
what they're doing. They're just minors.
They have to be protected and cared for
by adults. We know that, right?
We can't expect kids not to make mistakes.
They just need another chance!
Please, look at the screen.
This is the evidence we collected,
which shows the extent
of their drug business and network.
They have made over 50 million won
by selling drugs.
Incredible, isn't it?
Juvenile offenders?
Minors that need our protection?
Don't make me laugh.
What about their victims at school? Hm?
Who will protect them?
They didn't know!
It's okay, honey.
It's not too late to educate them now,
is it? They'll learn.
How about we all pitch in
for a settlement?
And with the money,
we'll compensate all the victims.
We just need to submit all of this
in writing. Isn't that correct?
We'll submit everything.
And we'll pay for whatever else is needed.
-Please, go easy on them, sir.
-Just this once.
They're still young children.
We wouldn't want to destroy their future
and have a few mistakes ruin their lives?
Shut up!
"Do unto others
what you would have them do unto you."
That is the fundamental law of society.
And that is what you
should have taught your children.
If you could not,
then the school should have.
And if the school couldn't do it,
then we as a society should've done it.
The Bureau has stepped in because
no one was able to teach them this lesson.
I assure you we will not fail.
We will teach them
that actions have consequences,
and they will never be allowed
to forget the agony they've caused.
This is how they will learn their lesson.
Mom, do something about this.
-Please?
-I will, sweetheart.
Oh, Ji-ung just told me
how much he regrets his actions.
Find it in your heart to forgive them.
You boys will never do this again, right?
No!
I was wrong!
I did something I shouldn't have.
I'm so sorry. I regret everything I did.
I won't ever do it again.
I just want to be given one more chance!
This is how it should have been
the first time.
Please, I can't go back there.
Please don't make me go back!
Don't ask us for forgiveness.
Ask your victim.
I will never…
ever forgive you for what you've done.
Ever since I met you guys,
my life has been torture.
Every day, I was terrified. I was
so scared that I could hardly breathe.
To me, school
was a living hell.
You can't escape me, kid.
I'll make this your personal hell!
I can play these games forever.
Why should I be the one to pay
when you are the guilty ones?
I don't wanna hurt anymore.
I want my life to keep going!
You still don't get it, do you?
I'm a juvenile offender,
which means I can get away
with killing you, you bitch!
Ji-ung, stop! Oh God!
The parents' request
for the release of their children
is now hereby officially denied.
-Officially denied?
-Don't do this, Minister!
You can't!
The boys will be taken back
to the detention center.
Oh no! You can't do this!
You can't do this to my son!
Ji-ung, no! No!
That's my son! Don't touch him! Don't!
-Please!
-Wait!
Min-su! Min-su!
Hey! Please, don't!
No, please don't take him from me!
Min-su! Min-su!
Thank you so much.
From now on, schools in Korea
will no longer accept students
with criminal records in the classroom.
For decades,
we have asked for legislative reform,
but nothing has been done.
In the meantime,
the number of crimes committed by minors
has continued to increase.
Because of this, innocent students
continue to suffer in school.
The Bureau will not stand for this. We
will protect them against the offenders.
Maybe you believe them to be innocent,
but to us,
they need to be taught a lesson.
Hey, the boys are back!
Did you miss me already?
I can't believe it.
Get inside.
It's time for you to pay the price, guys.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Get inside.
Feel the fear that you made them feel.
You'll learn a lot of things in here.
Come on.
All of you
How long will we have to stay here, sir?
Until you turn 18.
Then you'll be held accountable.
You'll pay for the things you've done.
Yun-jin! Yun-jin. I'm sorry.
Please, Yun-jin! Yun-jin, I was wrong.
I won't ever do it again.
Please just open the door. Please?
Yun-jin!
-Well done, everyone.
-Thank you.
-Appreciate it.
-Thanks.
Are you sure this is all you want?
Yes, sir.
This was the only thing I could think of.
All right, then.
Thank you for all your help.
Not at all.
I was the one who offered to help you.
But, please,
could you promise me just one thing?
Can you make sure
that no one turns out like me?
I think that the Bureau
could achieve that dream.
Pass me the ball!
Nice one, man.
So, can I really have this?
Just like the day we met
How can I let you go?
Hey, you newbie.
Yes, sir.
You've heard of the boss from the BS gang?
-Sure, but I swear, I didn't tell anyone.
-Ah, shh, you're good.
It's all right. Good work.
But you know our boss
can get a little paranoid, right?
Yes, sir.
Night, night.
Hey, hey, hey!